<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">See_U_Festival</string>
    <string name="fr_value">French</string>
    <string name="lang_header">Choose language</string>
    <string name="en_value">English</string>
    <string name="lang_title">Languages</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="option_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="nl_value">Dutch</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="a_propors">About</string>
    <string name="artistes">Artists</string>
    <string name="benevoles">Volunteers</string>
    <string name="festival">Festival</string>
    <string name="ticket">Tickets</string>
    <string name="description_benevole">Would you like to participate in setting up one of our festivals? Would you like to help our team in some way? Click on this button to become a volunteer!</string>
    <string name="become_benevole">Become a volunteer</string>
    <string name="description_un_mute">Un-Mute, it\'s the non-profit organization that finds you the little nuggets of the Belgian scene! The objective is simple: to make the local independent scene accessible to the public, thanks to the crowdfunding system applied to the world of festivals.</string>
    <string name="what_is_un_mute">Un-Mute it\'s...</string>
    <string name="description_ticket_combi">" Gives one person access to the entire festival. Participate in the validation of all posters (or only the poster of your favorite artist if you have one)."</string>
    <string name="description_ticket_combi_early">Gives one person access to the entire festival. Participate in the validation of all posters (or only the poster of your favorite artist if you have one). Early bird - these tickets will no longer be available after the validation date.</string>
    <string name="description_ticket_dimanche">Gives access to a person on Sunday, May 17. Participate in the validation of the posters of Saturday (or only of the poster of your favorite artist if you have one).</string>
    <string name="description_ticket_dimanche_early">" Gives access to a person on Sunday, May 17. Participate in the validation of the posters of Sunday (or only of the poster of your favorite artist if you have one). Early bird - these tickets will no longer be available after the validation date."</string>
    <string name="description_ticket_enfant_combi">Give access to a child under 12 to the entire festival. Participate in the validation of all posters (or only the poster of your favorite artist if you have one).</string>
    <string name="description_ticket_enfant_dimanche">Provides access to a child under the age of 12 on Sunday, May 17. Participate in the validation of the posters of Saturday (or only the poster of your favorite artist if you have one).</string>
    <string name="description_ticket_enfant_samedi">" Gives access to a child under 12 on Saturday May 16. Participate in the validation of the posters of Saturday (or only of the poster of your favorite artist if you have one)."</string>
    <string name="description_ticket_samedi">Gives access to a person on Saturday May 16. Participate in the validation of the posters of Saturday (or only the poster of your favorite artist if you have one).</string>
    <string name="description_ticket_samedi_early">Gives access to one person on the Saturday of the festival. Participate in the validation of the posters of Saturday (or only of the poster of your favorite artist if you have one). Early bird - these tickets will no longer be available after the validation date.</string>
    <string name="description_ab">" Electro-pop style artist from Liège. Self-taught musician. In the oven and in the mill, he writes, performs and composes songs in the English language, but also in Spanish, and more occasionally in French."</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>
    <string name="Sunday">Sunday</string>
    <string name="saturday">Saturday</string>
    <string name="see_u_space">"See U space "</string>
    <string name="festival_date">05/16/2020 - 05/17/2020</string>
    <string name="see_u_festival">"See U festival "</string>
    <string name="collaboratif">"Collaborative "</string>
    <string name="collab_description">The artists work together to fill the festival hall, united behind a common goal: the minimum number of tickets to validate the event.</string>
    <string name="local">Local</string>
    <string name="local_description">You don\'t always have to look very far to find talent... Near you, in your region, emerging artists are just waiting to be heard.</string>
    <string name="participatif">Participatory</string>
    <string name="participatif_description">Le festival est produit sur base du financement collectif. Acheter un ticket revient à participer directement à la production de l\'événement !</string>
    <string name="decouverte">Discovery</string>
    <string name="decouverte_description">Does your playlist always feature the same artists? But there\'s no shortage of variety. We\'ve found the nuggets for tomorrow!</string>
    <string name="biographie">Biography</string>
    <string name="ab_3">At the oven and the mill, he writes, interprets and composes songs in English, but also in Spanish and, more occasionally, in French.</string>
    <string name="ab_2">Self-taught musician.</string>
    <string name="ab_1">Artist from Liège with an electro-pop style.</string>
    <string name="scene_1">Stage 1</string>
    <string name="scene_2">Stage 2</string>
    <string name="scene_3">Stage 3</string>
    <string name="on_air">"ON AIR ! "</string>
    <string name="past">PAST</string>
    <string name="vectors_description">The Vectors is a rock band formed in 2015 following in the footsteps of English bands such as Arctic Monkeys or Muse with inspiration from muscular American bands such as Rage Against the Machine or Queens of the Stone Age.</string>
    <string name="yakhchal_description">A post rock trio composed of bass, guitar and drums. Yakhchal creates instrumental songs made of melancholic atmospheres and melodies, repetitive psychedelic loops and effects that evolve into explosive riffs.</string>
    <string name="dark_horse_description">At the begging- hop- in the middle- zoo- and then whack at the end.</string>
    <string name="funkthisship_description">Gravy-funk-rock alternative storytelling quartet.</string>
    <string name="profil">"Profile "</string>
</resources>